Finding Aid for Alvin M. Bentley Papers 1935-1969
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Congressional files 1952-1960
  - Yearly Files
    - 1956
      - Topical file 1956
        - Civil Aeronautics Administration (Box 11)
        - Commerce, Department of (Box 11)
        - Commissions: Atomic Energy; Civil Service; International Cooperation; Hoover; Interstate Commerce (Box 11)
        - Communism (Box 11)
        - Congressional Campaign, 4 folders (Box 11)
        - Defense, Department of, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Education, 3 folders (Box 12)
        - Education and Labor Committee (Box 12)
        - Federal Communication Commission (Box 12)
        - Foreign Affairs, 3 folders (Box 12)
        - Foreign Affairs-Bow Resolution (Box 12)
        - Foreign Affairs-Foreign Aid to India (Box 12)
        - Foreign Affairs-Foreign Aid, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Government Operations Committee (Box 12)
        - Health, Education & Welfare, Department of (Box 12)
        - Highways, 4 folders (Box 12)
        - Highway Taxes (Box 12)
        - Housing and Home Finance, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Hungary (Box 12)
        - Interior, Department of (Box 12)
        - Interior & Insular Affairs-Statehood for Alaska, Hawaii, Puerto Rico (Box 12)
        - International Affairs, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee (Box 12)
        - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee-Railroad Retirement (Box 12)
        - Immigration and Naturalization (Box 12)
        - Judiciary Committee, 4 folders (Box 13)
        - Justice (Box 13)
        - Labor, 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Liquor Advertising, 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Michigan, 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Michigan politics, 4 folders (Box 13)
        - Michigan Veterans Administration Hospitals (Box 13)
        - National Conference on Citizenship (Box 13)
        - Natural Gas, 2 folders (Box 13)
        - National Labor Relations Board (Box 13)
        - Politics, 6 folders (Box 13)
        - Post Office (Box 13)
        - Post Office and Civil Service Committee, 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Public Works Committee-Saginaw Valley Flood Control, 7 folders (Box 13)
        - Public Works Committee-Saginaw Valley Flood Control, 1 folders (Box 14)
        - Puerto Rico (Box 14)
        - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 14)
        - Small Business Administration (Box 14)
        - State, Department of-Arab-Israeli Dispute (Box 14)
        - State, Department of-General (Box 14)
        - Social Security, 3 folders (Box 14)
        - Taxation of Cooperatives (Box 14)
        - Tariff and trade, 2 folders (Box 14)
        - United Nations (Box 14)
        - Veterans, 6 folders (Box 14)
        - Ways and Means Committee, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - 1957
      - Correspondence
        - January-April 1957, 11 folders (Box 14)
        - May-December 1957, 13 folders (Box 15)
      - Topical file 1957
        - Agriculture, 10 folders (Box 15)
        - Agriculture-Soil Conservation (Box 15)
        - Agriculture-Wheat, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Appropriations Committee, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Armed Services Committee (Box 15)
        - Atomic Energy-Joint Committee (Box 15)
        - Banking and Currency, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Budget Bureau, 7 folders (Box 15)
        - Budget Bureau (cont.), 3 folders (Box 16)
        - Civil Service Commission (Box 16)
        - Communism (Box 16)
        - Defense, Department of the Army, 4 folders (Box 16)
        - Defense, Department of the Navy (Box 16)
        - Defense, Department of-Missiles and Satellites (Box 16)
        - Defense, Department of-Miscellaneous (Box 16)
        - Eastern Europe (Box 16)
        - Education, 4 folders (Box 16)
        - Education and Labor Committee (Box 16)
        - Elderly workers-employment, 2 folders (Box 16)
        - Excise tax (Box 16)
        - Federal Communication Commission, 2 folders (Box 16)
        - Federal Power Commission (Box 16)
        - Foreign Affairs Committee, 3 folders (Box 16)
        - Foreign Aid, 5 folders (Box 16)
        - Government Operations Committee (Box 16)
        - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of (Box 16)
        - Hoover Commission, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - House Administration Committee, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Hungary, 8 folders (Box 17)
        - Immigration and Naturalization, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Income tax-personal, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Income tax-personal, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Income tax-corporate (Box 17)
        - Interior, Department of (Box 17)
        - Interior & Insular Affairs, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Interior & Insular Affairs-Statehood for Alaska, Hawaii (Box 17)
        - International Affairs, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Interstate & Foreign Commerce Committee-Pay TV (Box 17)
        - Interstate & Foreign Commerce Committee-Liquor (Box 17)
        - Interstate & Foreign Commerce Committee-Advertising, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Interstate & Foreign Commerce Committee-Natural Gas (Box 17)
        - Interstate & Foreign Commerce Committee-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Judiciary Committee, 7 folders (Box 17)
        - Judiciary-Robinson-Patman Act (Equality of Opportunity in Business) (Box 18)
        - Labor, 4 folders (Box 18)
        - Michigan, 4 folders (Box 18)
        - Middle East, 3 folders (Box 18)
        - Mobile Office (Box 18)
        - Poland, 2 folders (Box 18)
        - Political (Box 18)
        - Political-Michigan, 4 folders (Box 18)
        - Post Office, 2 folders (Box 18)
        - Postal Rate Increase (Box 18)
        - Postal Salary Increase, 6 folders (Box 18)
        - Puerto Rico (Box 18)
        - Public Works Committee: Saginaw Valley Flood Control Program, 4 folders (Box 18)
        - Rules Committee (Box 19)
        - Small Business, 2 folders (Box 19)
        - Social Security, 4 folders (Box 19)
        - State, Department of (Box 19)
        - Tariff & Trade (Box 19)
        - Taxation (Box 19)
        - Taxation of Cooperatives (Box 19)
        - Treasury, Department of (Box 19)
        - United Nations (Box 19)
        - United States Information Agency, 3 folders (Box 19)
        - Veterans Affairs, 9 folders (Box 19)
        - Ways and Means Committee, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - 1958
      - Correspondence
        - January-April 1958, 16 folders (Box 19)
        - May-December 1958, 23 folders (Box 20)
      - Topical file 1958
        - Agriculture-General, 3 folders (Box 20)
        - Agriculture-dairy, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Agriculture-farm program (Box 20)
        - Agriculture-humane slaughtering (Box 20)
        - Agriculture-soil conservation-general (Box 20)
        - Agriculture-soil conservation: Misterguay Creek Project [Saginaw, Shiawasee & Genesee Counties], 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Agriculture-Wheat, 5 folders (Box 20)
        - AFL-CIO (Box 20)
        - Appropriations Committee (Box 20)
        - Armed Services Committee (Box 20)
        - Assembly of Captive European Nations (Box 20)
        - Banking and Currency, 3 folders (Box 21)
        - Blind, legislative support of, 3 folders (Box 21)
        - Citizens Foreign Relations Committee, 2 folders (Box 21)
        - Civil Aeronautics Administration-Tri-Cities Airport, 3 folders (Box 21)
        - Commerce, Department of (Box 21)
        - Communism (Box 21)
        - Department of-general, 2 folders (Box 21)
        - Department of Defense-Army (Box 21)
        - Department of Defense-Navy (Box 21)
        - Department of Defense-Saginaw Reserve Unit (Box 21)
        - Economics, 3 folders (Box 21)
        - Education, 3 folders (Box 21)
        - Excise tax, 2 folders (Box 21)
        - Federal Trade Commission (Box 21)
        - Foreign Affairs Committee, 4 folders (Box 21)
        - Foreign Affairs Committee (cont.), 3 folders (Box 22)
        - Foreign Aid, 5 folders (Box 22)
        - Government Operations Committee (Box 22)
        - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Housing & Home Finance, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Hungary, 3 folders (Box 22)
        - Income tax, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Interior & Insular Affairs-Statehood for Alaska and Hawaii (Box 22)
        - International Affairs, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Interstate & Foreign Commerce Committee-General, 4 folders (Box 22)
        - Interstate & Foreign Commerce Committee-Railroads, 6 folders (Box 22)
        - Judiciary Committee, 5 folders (Box 23)
        - Justice, Department of (Box 23)
        - Labor-general, 10 folders (Box 23)
        - Labor-rank & file control of unions, 3 folders (Box 23)
        - Labor-Chicano labor, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - Michigan, 4 folders (Box 23)
        - Michigan-politics, 3 folders (Box 23)
        - Middle East, 3 folders (Box 23)
        - Mobile Office (Box 23)
        - National Conference on Citizenship (Box 23)
        - Political, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - Post Office (Box 23)
        - Postal Services (Box 23)
        - Public Works Committee-Saginaw Valley, 4 folders (Box 24)
        - Public Works Committee-Flood Control Project, 2 folders (Box 24)
        - Social Security, 4 folders (Box 24)
        - State, Department of, 4 folders (Box 24)
        - Taft-Hartley (Box 24)
        - Tariff & Trade, 3 folders (Box 24)
        - Taxes (Box 24)
        - Taxation of cooperatives (Box 24)
        - Treasury, Department of (Box 24)
        - United Nations (Box 24)
        - Veterans, 3 folders (Box 24)
        - Ways and Means (Box 24)
    - 1959
      - Correspondence
        - January-February 1959, 8 folders (Box 24)
        - March-December 1959, 32 folders (Box 25)
      - Topical File 1959
        - Agriculture, 8 folders (Box 26)
        - AFL-CIO (Box 26)
        - Appropriations Committee (Box 26)
        - Armed Services Committee (Box 26)
        - Astronautics and Space Exploration Committee (Box 26)
        - Atomic Energy, Joint Committee On (Box 26)
        - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 26)
        - Banking and Currency, 5 folders (Box 26)
        - Bureau of the Budget, 5 folders (Box 26)
        - Chicano Farm Labor, 3 folders (Box 26)
        - Civil Aeronautics Administration (Box 26)
        - Communism, 2 folders (Box 26)
        - Commission on Metropolitan Government (Box 26)
        - Commerce, Department of (Box 26)
        - Defense, Department of, 5 folders (Box 27)
        - Economics (Box 27)
        - Education, 3 folders (Box 27)
        - Educational television (Box 27)
        - Excise tax, 5 folders (Box 27)
        - Federal Aviation Administration (Box 27)
        - Federal Communication Commission (Box 27)
        - Federal Trade Commission, 8 folders (Box 27)
        - Foreign Affairs Committee, 4 folders (Box 27)
        - Foreign Affairs Committee, 3 folders (Box 28)
        - Foreign Affairs Committee: United Kingdom Study Mission (Box 28)
        - Foreign Aid, 7 folders (Box 28)
        - Germany, 2 folders (Box 28)
        - Government Operations Committee (Box 28)
        - Health, Education & Welfare, Department of, 2 folders (Box 28)
        - Highways, 2 folders (Box 28)
        - Housing, 2 folders (Box 28)
        - Hungary (Box 28)
        - Income Tax, 6 folders (Box 28)
        - Interior, Department of (Box 28)
        - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee-General (Box 28)
        - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee-Statehood for Alaska & Hawaii (Box 28)
        - International Affairs (Box 28)
        - Interstate & Foreign Commerce Committee, 3 folders (Box 28)
        - Judiciary Committee, 6 folders (Box 29)
        - Justice, Department of (Box 29)
        - Labor, 15 folders (Box 29)
        - Michigan, 5 folders (Box 29)
        - Michigan-politics, 4 folders (Box 30)
        - National Conference on Citizenship (Box 30)
        - Poland (Box 30)
        - Politics, 4 folders (Box 30)
        - Post Office, 5 folders (Box 30)
        - Public Health (Box 30)
        - Public Works Committee, 2 folders (Box 30)
        - Puerto Rico (Box 30)
        - Republican State Committee (Box 30)
        - Small Business Administration, 3 folders (Box 30)
        - Social Security, 7 folders (Box 30)
        - State Department of, 3 folders (Box 31)
        - Taxes, 3 folders (Box 31)
        - Taxation of Cooperatives (Box 31)
        - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 31)
        - Turkey (Box 31)
        - Un-American Activities Committee (Box 31)
        - United Nations (Box 31)
        - United States Information Agency (Box 31)
        - Veterans, 6 folders (Box 31)
        - Ways and Means Committee, 4 folders (Box 31)
    - 1960
      - Correspondence
        - January-May 1960, 16 folders (Box 31)
        - June-December 1960, 15 folders (Box 32)
      - Topical File 1960
        - Agriculture, 4 folders (Box 32)
        - AFL-CIO (Box 32)
        - Armed Services Committee (Box 32)
        - Assembly of Captive European Nations (Box 32)
        - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 32)
        - Civil Aeronautics Administration (Box 32)
        - Civil Rights, 3 folders (Box 32)
        - Commerce, Department of (Box 32)
        - Communism (Box 32)
        - Cuba (Box 32)
        - Defense, Department of, 2 folders (Box 32)
        - Education and Labor Committee (Box 32)
        - Economics (Box 32)
        - Excise Tax (Box 32)
        - Federal Aid to Schools, 2 folders (Box 32)
        - Federal Aid to Schools (cont.), 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Federal Communication Commission (Box 33)
        - Federal Power Commission (Box 33)
        - Federal Trade Commission, 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Foreign Affairs Committee, 7 folders (Box 33)
        - Foreign Aid, 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission (Box 33)
        - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of, 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Housing Administration (Box 33)
        - Income Tax (Box 33)
        - Interior, Department of (Box 33)
        - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee (Box 33)
        - International Affairs (Box 33)
        - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (Box 33)
        - Judiciary Committee, 2 folders (Box 34)
        - Labor, 4 folders (Box 34)
        - Michigan, 2 folders (Box 34)
        - Minimum Wage, 2 folders (Box 34)
        - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 34)
        - National Labor Relations Board (Box 34)
        - Public Works Commission, 2 folders (Box 34)
        - Republican Party (Box 34)
        - Post Office & Civil Service Commission, 5 folders (Box 34)
        - Selective Service (Box 34)
        - Social Security, 6 folders (Box 34)
        - Social Security (cont.), 11 folders (Box 35)
        - State, Department of (Box 35)
        - Tariff & Trade (Box 35)
        - Taxes (Box 35)
        - Un-American Activities Committee (Box 35)
        - Veterans, 3 folders (Box 35)
        - Ways and Means Committee (Box 35)
  - Speeches, etc.
    - SOS Club, Washington,D.C. 1955-1960 (Box 35)
    - Samuel Alexander Mudd memorial materials 1953-1963 (Box 35)
    - Speeches 1949-1950 (Box 35)
    - Newspaper columns 1950 (Box 35)
    - Speeches March-September 1951 (Box 35)
    - Speeches October-December 1951 (Box 35)
    - Speeches 1951 undated, 4 folders (Box 35)
    - Newspaper articles 1951, 3 folders (Box 35)
    - Speeches January-July 1952 (Box 35)
    - Speeches August-December 1952 (Box 35)
    - Speeches January-April 1953 (Box 36)
    - Speeches, May-August 1953 (Box 36)
    - Speeches September-December 1953 (Box 36)
    - Speeches 1953 (undated) (Box 36)
    - Speaking engagements 1953 (Box 36)
    - Speeches January-March 1954 (Box 36)
    - Speeches April-May 1954 (Box 36)
    - Speeches June 1954 (Box 36)
    - Speeches July 1954 (Box 36)
    - Speeches August-September 1954 (Box 36)
    - Speeches October-December 1954 (Box 36)
    - Speeches 1954 (undated) (Box 36)
    - Speaking engagements 1954 (Box 36)
    - Speeches January-February 1955 (Box 36)
    - Speeches March-April 1955 (Box 36)
    - Speeches, May-June 1955 (Box 36)
    - Speeches July-August 1955 (Box 36)
    - Speeches September-December 1955 (Box 36)
    - Speeches 1955 (undated) (Box 36)
    - Speaking engagements 1955 (Box 36)
    - Speeches January 1956 (Box 36)
    - Speeches February 1956 (Box 36)
    - Speeches March-April 1956 (Box 36)
    - Speeches, May-June 1956 (Box 36)
    - Speeches, July-December and undated 1956 (Box 36)
    - Speaking Engagements 1956 (Box 36)
    - Speeches January 1957 (Box 36)
    - Speeches February-April 1957 (Box 36)
    - Speeches, May-June 1957 (Box 36)
    - Speeches July-December 1957 (Box 36)
    - Speeches 1957 (undated) (Box 36)
    - Speaking Engagements 1957 (Box 36)
    - Speeches January 1959 (Box 36)
    - Speeches February 1959 (Box 36)
    - Speeches March 1959 (Box 36)
    - Speeches April-May 1959 (Box 36)
    - Speeches June 1959 (Box 37)
    - Speeches July 1959 (Box 37)
    - Speeches August-September 1959 (Box 37)
    - Speeches 1959 (undated) (Box 37)
    - Television program January-February 1959 (Box 37)
    - Television program March-April 1959 (Box 37)
    - Television program, May-June 1959 (Box 37)
    - Television program July-August 1959 (Box 37)
    - Speaking engagements 1959 (Box 37)
    - Speeches January-February 1960 (Box 37)
    - Speeches March-May 1960 (Box 37)
    - Speeches July-December 1960 (Box 37)
    - Speeches October 1960 (Wayne State University) (Box 37)
    - Speaking engagements 1960 (Box 37)
    - Congressional Bulletins
      - 1953-1956 (Box 37)
      - 1957-1960 (Box 37)
    - Speeches undated (Box 37)
  - Post Office Patronage Files
    - Owosso Post Office 1958-1959 (Box 37)
    - Ionia County Post Office Files
      - Belding
        - 1955-April, 1957 (Box 37)
        - May 1957-1960 (Box 37)
      - Clarksville 1957-1960 (Box 37)
      - Ionia
        - 1952-1955 (Box 37)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 37)
        - 1958-1961 (Box 37)
      - Lake Odessa 1956-1959 (Box 37)
      - Lyons 1956-1959 (Box 37)
      - Orleans 1955-1961 (Box 37)
      - Palo 1958-1962 (Box 37)
      - Pewamo
        - 1955-1957 (Box 37)
        - 1958-1961 (Box 37)
      - Portland
        - 1953-1957 (Box 37)
        - 1958 (Box 37)
        - 1960 (Box 37)
      - Saranac 1957-1958 (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Congressional diary 1953-1960 (Box 38)
    - Legislation and Resolutions introduced (Box 38)
    - Voting Record
      - 1953-1955 (Box 38)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 38)
      - 1960 (Box 38)
    - Questionnaires 1953-1959 (Box 38)
    - Republican party-miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - The DACOR Bulletin (official organ of Diplomatic and Consular Officers Retired) 1954-1958 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous materials concerning UAW-CIO (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous concerning Veterans Administration Hospitals 1949, 1952 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 38)
    - Printed materials on assorted topics (Box 38)
    - Notebook containing information on bill to amend United States Information and Educational Exchange Act of 1948 (Box 38)
    - Notebook containing Bentley's Congressional voting record, topically and alphabetically arranged (Box 38)
- Senatorial Campaign 1960
  Senatorial Campaign (5 linear ft., 1958-1960) consists of two subseries. There is a topical file containing correspondence, clippings, and printed material on subjects pertaining to the issues and mechanics of the 1960 election. This file was maintained by the Bentley office. The other subseries draws together the remaining campaign files. Here have been brought together correspondence with campaign workers, press releases, clippings, and itineraries.
  - Alphabetical File
    (correspondence, clippings, printed materials and miscellaneous)
    - "A" (Box 39)
    - Advertising-Radio, TV, Newspapers, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Applications-general (Box 39)
    - Applications-Professional, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - "B" (Box 39)
    - Bagwell for Governor-Itinerary (Box 39)
    - Bentley Owosso Office Correspondence (Box 39)
    - Bentley Washington Office Correspondence (Box 39)
    - Bentley Biographical Sketch (short form) (Box 39)
    - Bentley Biographical Sketch (long form) (Box 39)
    - Bentley Thank-You Notes (outgoing) (Box 39)
    - Bentley Thank-You Notes (incoming) (Box 39)
    - "C", 3 folders (Box 39)
    - Campaign Advertising (Box 39)
    - Campaign Data-samples (Box 39)
    - Campaign literature, letters, give-away items (Box 39)
    - Campaign literature-general (Box 39)
    - Campaign staff and staff meetings (Box 39)
    - Cannevan, John P (Box 39)
    - Caruso, Dick (Box 39)
    - Caswell, William (Box 39)
    - Congratulatory (Box 39)
    - Crank File (Box 39)
    - "D" (Box 39)
    - Degnan, Dan D (Box 39)
    - Denison, Spencer (Box 39)
    - Des Jardin, Norman (Box 39)
    - Directories (Box 39)
    - Doctors' Mailing List (Box 39)
    - "E" (Box 39)
    - Election Qualifications (Box 39)
    - Elligan, Leon (Box 39)
    - Employment applications (Box 39)
    - Endorsements (Box 39)
    - Ethnic Groups (Box 39)
    - Events during election year (Box 39)
    - "F" (Box 39)
    - "G" (Box 39)
    - Glynn, James (Box 39)
    - "H" (Box 39)
    - Hotel-Motel Facilities (Box 39)
    - Hungarian Group (Box 39)
    - "I" (Box 39)
    - Itineraries-general (Box 39)
    - "J" (Box 39)
    - Joseph, Thomas, B, 6 folders (Box 40)
    - "K" (Box 40)
    - "L" (Box 40)
    - Labor: CIO-COPE (Campaign literature & miscellaneous) (Box 40)
    - "Mc" (Box 40)
    - McNamara, Patrick, 4 folders (Box 40)
    - "M" (Box 40)
    - Miscellaneous, 5 folders (Box 40)
    - "N" (Box 40)
    - Negro Group (Box 40)
    - "O" (Box 40)
    - Opinions regarding Senatorial Campaign (Box 40)
    - Organizational Meetings, 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Owosso Republican Women (Box 40)
    - "P" (Box 40)
    - Polish Group (Box 40)
    - Polish Committee-Walter Wosoca (Box 40)
    - Press Kit (Box 40)
    - Promotional Material (Box 40)
    - Promotional material-Promotion for Ticket splitting (Box 40)
    - "R" (Box 40)
    - Reference Letters (Box 40)
    - Reid, Bill (Box 40)
    - Republican Congressional Committee-Newsletter (Box 40)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 40)
    - Republican Nominees (Box 40)
    - Republican State Central Committee, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Republican State Convention, 1958-Delegates (Box 41)
    - Republican State Committee-volunteers (Box 41)
    - Republican Women (Box 41)
    - Requests for Literature-miscellaneous (Box 41)
    - "S" (Box 41)
    - Sample Campaign Letters (Box 41)
    - Statutes regarding elections (Box 41)
    - "T" (Box 41)
    - Telegrams, received (Box 41)
    - Telegrams, sent (Box 41)
    - Television
      - November 7, 1960 program (questions and answers) (Box 41)
      - Primary Election costs (Box 41)
      - proposed budget (Box 41)
      - proposed spots (Box 41)
      - spots (July 5-August 1) (Box 41)
    - Thomas, Leigh
      - general (Box 41)
      - personal memoranda (Box 41)
    - Thank-You notes from People Invited to June 4, 1960 meeting (Box 41)
    - Thank You letters sent (Box 41)
    - Travis, Noble (Box 41)
    - "U" (Box 41)
    - United States Government (Box 41)
    - "V" (Box 41)
    - Volunteer Workers
      - general (Box 41)
      - Republican Party (Box 41)
    - "W" (Box 41)
    - Washington Office (Box 41)
    - "XYZ" (Box 41)
    - Young, Arthur & Co. (Box 41)
    - Young Republicans (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous campaign files
    - Campaign Workers, A-Z, 24 folders (Box 41)
    - Campaign Workers by County
      - Alcona-Arenac (Box 41)
      - Baraga-Branch (Box 41)
      - Calhoun-Clare (Box 41)
      - Clinton-Crawford (Box 41)
      - Delta-Gratiot (Box 41)
      - Hillsdale-Ingham (Box 41)
      - Ionia-Jackson (Box 41)
      - Kalamazoo (Box 41)
      - Kalkaska-Kent (Box 41)
      - Keweenaw-Luce (Box 41)